앱 스토어에 앱을 올리기 위해서는 다음과 같은 자료가 필요하다.

- 앱의 아이콘
	프로젝트 파일에 포함되어있습니다.

- 앱의 정확한 영문이름
	한글 : 너의 막차를 지켜줄게
	영문 : save your last metro

- 앱의 설명문 (언어별)
	
한글 :

혹시 학교나 회사 근처에서 음주를 즐기고 계실 때 막차나 통금 시간 걱정 때문에 수시로 시간을 확인하신 적 없으신가요? 저희는 그런 통근, 통학러들을 위해 이 앱을 준비하였습니다.
터치 한번으로 인근 지하철 역의 도착 정보를 바로 확인하세요. 원하는 정보를 얻는데는 터치 한번과 3초면 충분합니다. 

영문 :

if you are living in Seoul or nearby in South Korea and you just always take subway to get to the work place, you can't help but consider when you should go out to take your metro, espetially when you are drinking in late-night near there. you maybe can't always take surcharge-taxi for return, or you've been already on finantial difficulties.

this app help you know when trains arrive to the nearest station(from where you are). until getting the information you need, it just takes 3 seconds with only one touch. it will just make you absolutely satisfied with its accurancy, reliablility and rapid response time.

- 앱의 스크린 샷 (언어별)
	스크린샷 폴더에 첨부하였습니다.

- 앱의 키워드
	막차, 지하철, 도착 정보, 교통, 생활 편의
	last train, last metro, traffic information, subway, metro
